Orange字幕组
倾情制作
时轴 小白龙 大周
翻译 糊糊 阿薇 浅蓝 战弈 踏空
校对 战奕 派派
特效 十尺
压制 联盟少侠
神奇动物在哪里
Fantastic beasts and where to find them
盖勒特 格林德沃
黑巫师再次于欧洲发动袭击
霍格沃兹魔法学校
加强安保
黑巫师
恐怖威胁
布朗克斯"花瓶"女巫
巫师的困惑
足球是麻鸡世界的魁地奇吗
格林德沃攻势猛烈
麻瓜面临战争威胁
美方继续执行神奇动物禁令
史上最严之年
反巫师的呼声水涨船高
皮克丽安顿民怨
女巫因伪造魔杖持有证遭指控
格林德沃身藏何处
针对格林德沃进行调查
还有人是安全的吗
格林德沃闹得人心惶惶
杜戈尔 安分点 好不
Dougal... you settle down now, please.
马上就到了
It won't be long.
下一个
Next.
- 英国来的 - 没错 - 第一次来纽约 - 是的
British, huh? -Yes. -First trip to New York? -Yes.
- 有携带食物吗 - 没有
Anything edible in there? -No.
家禽呢
Livestock?
这破烂是该修修了...呃 也没有
Must get that fixed... ahh, no.
打开我瞅瞅
Let me take a look.
麻瓜模式
- 欢迎来到纽约 - 谢谢
- Welcome to New York. -Thank you.
下一个
Next!
它就好像...好像一阵风..如鬼魅一般
And it was like a... like a wind or like a... like a ghost...
漆黑一片...但我看到了它的眼睛
but dark... and I saw its eyes.
眼里泛着白光
Shinin' white eyes...
- 一阵带眼睛的...黑风 - 就是一团黑
- A dark wind... with eyes. -Like a dark mass,
潜行到那儿 遁入地中
and it dove down there, down underground.
总有人得管管这事儿吧
Someone ought do something about it.
它无处不在 我们又无能为力
It's everywhere this thing. It's out of control.
嘿 得到什么线索了吗 - 黑风什么什么之类乱七八糟的
Hey, did you get anything? -Dark wind, blah blah.
可能就是由大气或雷暴导致的
It's some atmospheric hooey. Or electrical.
- 嘿 你渴吗 - 不了 我正在戒酒
- Hey, you thirsty? - Nah, I'm on the wagon.
答应了玛莎要戒的
Promised Martha I'd lay off.
是天气原因
It's atmospheric.
这伟大的城市因人类的发明而流光溢彩
This great city sparkles with the jewels of man's invention!
电影院 汽车 无线设备 电灯
Movie theaters, automobiles, the wireless, electric lights.
- 琳琅满目的设施使我们沉醉 - 不好意思
All dazzle and bewitch us! - So sorry.
但朋友们 福兮 祸之所伏
But where there is light there is shadow, friend.
有东西潜伏在我们身边
Something is stalking our city,
肆虐破坏又悄然无踪
wreaking destruction and then disappearing without a trace.
听我说 我们要去抗争 加入我们
Listen to me. We have to fight, join us,
第二塞勒姆人协会 为之而战
the Second Salemers, in our fight!
- 美女借过一下 - 你们听到我说的吗
- Excuse me, doll. - You hear me?
我只是想挤到银行那边去 - 我们必须众志成城
Just trying to get to the bank. -We have to fight together...
- 美女借过一下 - 你们听到我说的吗
- Excuse me, doll. - You hear me?
我只是想挤到银行那边去 - 我们必须众志成城
Just trying to get to the bank. -We have to fight together...
- 借过一下 我想 - 小心点 - 对不起 怪我的箱子
Excuse me, trying... -Watch it! -So sorry, my case.
我只是想挤到银行那边去 - 我们必须众志成城
Just trying to get to the bank. -We have to fight together...
- 借过一下 我想 - 小心点 - 对不起 怪我的箱子
Excuse me, trying... -Watch it! -So sorry, my case.
没事没事
No harm done.
- 借过 - 这位朋友
- Excuse me! -You, friend!
你今天为什么要来到我们的会场
What drew you to our meeting today?
我只是路过 - 你在寻找些什么吗
Oh... I was just passing. -Are you a seeker?
你在追求真相吗
A seeker after truth?
说真的 我远不止是一个追求者
I'm more of a chaser, really.
听我所言 留心我所警告的
Hear my words and heed my warning.
谁觉得好笑的 你笑一下试试
And laugh if you dare.
巫师就藏在我们身边
Witches live among us!
我们必须万众一心
We have to fight together for
为了子孙后代 为了未来着想
the sake of our children, for the sake of tomorrow!
这位朋友 你怎么看
What do you say to that, friend?
借过下
Excuse me.
有什么能帮到您的吗 先生
Can I help you, sir?
不用 我只是.. 在等人
No, I was just... just... waiting.
嗨
Hi.
- 你为什么来这 - 和你一样
- What brings you here? - Same as you...
- 你也是来这贷款开一家面包房的吗 - 是的
You're here to get a loan to open up a bakery? -Yes.
竟然有这种事
What are the odds of that?
- 那么 祝愿优秀的人都能成功 - 抱歉
- Well, may the best man win, I guess. -Excuse me.
嘿 先生...先生
Hey, mister... Hey, mister!
- 嘿 兄弟 - 科瓦尔斯基先生 您现在可以见宾利先生了
Hey, fella! -Mr. Kowalski, Mr. Bingley will see you now.
好吧...
Okay... Okay.
你目前就职于一家罐头厂对吗
You are currently working in a canning factory?
这已经是我能找到的最好的工作了 我1924年才回的国...
That's the best I can do... I only got back in '24.
- 回国 - 从欧洲 先生
Got back? -From Europe, sir.
是的 我是美国远征军的一员
Yeah... I was part of the Expeditionary Forces there.
- 好的 - 科瓦尔斯基先生 - 你得尝尝这油炸圈饼
- All right. -Mr. Kowalski. -You gotta try the paczki. Okay?
这是我奶奶祖传的秘方 香橙味的
It's my grandmother's recipe, the orange zest... just...
科瓦尔斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski, what do you
你打算提供什么给银行作为抵押
propose to offer the bank as collateral?
- 抵押 - 对
Collateral? -Collateral.
现在已经有
There are machines now that
能在一小时内做几百个甜甜圈的机器了
can produce hundreds of doughnuts an hour...
我懂 我懂 可我一无所有
I know, I know, but they're nothing like what I can do.
银行不能有坏账 科瓦尔斯基先生
The bank must be protected, Mr. Kowalski.
祝您好运
Good day to you.
嘿 英国先生 我觉得你的蛋快要孵化了
Hey, Mr. English guy! I think your egg is hatching.
- 什么 - 刚刚发生了什么
What? What just happened?
但是
But...
容我缓个神
Excuse me...
我当时在那儿....吗
I was... over there. I was... over there?
- 老实待着... -您好
In you hop... -Hello?
不 大家给我安分点 好好待着
No. Everyone settle down. Stay.
杜戈尔 别逼我进来收拾你
Dougal, don't make me come in there.
别逼我进来收拾你
Don't make me come down there.
别这样 开锁咒
Absolutely not! Alohomora!
所以你们打算偷钱吗
Oh, so you're gonna steal the money, huh?
通通石化
Petrificus Totalus!
宾利先生
Mr. Bingley!
科瓦尔斯基
Kowalski!
玩真的吗
Really?
不 看呐
No... Look at that. Look.
不不不 别开枪
Oh no... No, no, no. Don't shoot. Don't shoot!
想怎样 这是你最后一次顺手牵羊
What? For the last time, you pilfering pest...
把你的小爪子伸向那些不属于你的东西了
paws off what doesn't belong to you.
我真的很抱歉害你卷进来
I'm awfully sorry about all that.
- 那是什么鬼 - 你不需要了解
What the hell was that? - Nothing that need concern you.
很不幸你已经知道的太多了
Now unfortunately you have seen far too much,
所以如果你不介意
so if you wouldn't mind...
就直接站在这里
if you just stand there,
- 一眨眼功夫就结束 - 好的没问题
this will be over in a jiffy. -Sure, yeah.
对不起
Sorry...
混蛋
Bugger.
- 你是谁 - 我很抱歉
Who are you? -I'm sorry?
- 你是谁 - 纽特·斯卡曼德
Who are you? -Newt Scamander.
- 你呢 - 你包里装的是什么
And you are? -What's that thing in your case?
那是我的嗅嗅
That's my Niffler.
- 你脸上有脏东西 - 为什么在
You've got something on your... -Why in
萨勒姆女巫这么严厉的监管下 你还让它跑出来
the name of Deliverance Dane did you let that thing loose?
我不是故意的 他一看到闪闪发光的东西
I didn't mean to, he's incorrigible,
你懂的 就控制不住自己
you see, anything shiny, he's all over the place.
- 你不是故意的 - 不是故意的
You didn't mean to? -No.
你懂的 就控制不住自己
you see, anything shiny, he's all over the place.
- 你不是故意的 - 不是故意的
You didn't mean to? -No.
你可不能把那动物放出来乱跑
You could not have chosen a worse time to let that creature loose!
尤其在这个节骨眼上
We're in the middle of a situation here!
- 我逮捕你 - 你要把我带去哪
I'm taking you in. -You're taking me where?
美国魔法委员会
Magical Congress of the United States of America.
所以 你为美魔会工作吗
So, you work for MACUSA?
你是干什么的 侦查员之类么
What are you, some kind of investigator?
你能告诉我你是怎么处理那个麻鸡的吗
Can you please tell me you took care of the No-Maj?
- 什么 - 麻鸡 就是不会魔法的 不是巫师的普通人
- The what? -The No-Maj! No-magic... the non-wizard!
- 抱歉 我们把他们称作麻瓜 - 你清除他的记忆了吧
- Oh, sorry, we call them Muggles. -You wiped his memory, right?
那个提行李箱的麻鸡
The No-Maj with the case?
魔法规章3A条款 斯卡曼德先生 我这就逮捕你
That's a Section 3A, Mr. Scamander. I'm taking you in.
走吧
Come on.
对不起 但我现在要事在身
Er... sorry, but I do have things to do,
没骗你 - 那你恐怕得重新安排它们了
actually. -Well, you'll have to rearrange them!
你到底来纽约干什么
What are you doing in New York anyway?
我来买一件生日礼物
I came to buy a birthday present.
在伦敦就买不到吗
Couldn't you have done that in London?
真买不到 全世界只有一个
No, there's only one breeder of Appaloosa Puffskeins
阿帕卢萨小毛球的饲养者 他就住在纽约
in the world and he lives in New York, so no.
我抓了个违反3A条款的
I got a Section 3A.
顺便告诉你 我们不允许
By the way, we don't allow
在纽约饲养神奇动物
the breeding of magical creatures in New York.
我们一年前就把那人抓起来了
We closed that guy down a year ago.
- 嘿 戈德斯坦 - 嘿 瑞德
Hey, Goldstein. -Hey, Red.
- 去重案调查部 - 我还以为你
Major Investigation Department. -I thought you was...
去重案调查部 我抓了个违反3A的
Major Investigation Department! I got a Section 3A!
魔法引发骚乱
巫师面临暴露风险
国际联合会
The International Confederation
威胁说要派出代表团
is threatening to send a delegation.
他们认为这跟格林德沃在欧洲的袭击有关
They think this is related to Grindelwald's attacks in Europe.
我当时在场 那是个神奇动物
I was there. This is a beast.
它们的能力是人类无法企及的 主席阁下
No human could do what this thing is capable of, Madam President.
无论如何 有一件事是明确的 这种状况必须要遏制
Whatever it is, one thing's clear, it must be stopped.
现在麻鸡们备受恐慌
It's terrorizing No-Majs
当麻鸡们害怕的时候 它们就会发动革命
and when No-Majs are afraid, they attack.
这就意味着暴露 意味着战争
This could mean exposure. It could mean war.
我已经说得很清楚了吧 戈德斯坦恩小姐
I made your position here quite clear, Miss Goldstein.
Auror 傲罗
是一群如军人般
抗击黑魔法的
精英男女巫师
任务在于寻找
黑巫师并击溃他们
- 是的 主席阁下 - 你不再是一名傲罗了
Yes, Madam President, but I... -You are no longer an Auror.
- 对 主席阁下 但... - 戈德斯坦恩
- No, Madam President, but... -Goldstein.
- 我这出了点小意外 - 我告诉你
There's been a minor incident... -Well,
这间办公室不是用来处理鸡毛蒜皮小事的
this office is currently concerned with very major incidents.
- 我这出了点小意外 - 我告诉你
There's been a minor incident... -Well,
这间办公室不是用来处理鸡毛蒜皮小事的
this office is currently concerned with very major incidents.
- 出去 - 是的 阁下
Get out. -Yes, ma'am.
魔杖许可办公室
所以 你办了魔杖使用许可证吗
So, you got your wand permit?
在纽约 所有的外籍人士都得办这个证
All foreigners have to have them in New York.
申请邮件我几个星期前就已经寄出了
I made a postal application weeks ago.
斯卡曼德...你之前是呆在赤道几内亚吗
Scamander... And you were just in Equatorial Guinea?
我在外考察了整整一年
I've just completed a year in the field.
我正在写一本关于神奇动物的书
I'm writing a book about magical creatures.
一本猎杀指南么
Like... an extermination guide?
不 一本帮助人们
No. A guide to help people
正确认识并保护那些神奇动物们的书
understand why we should be protecting these creatures
- 而不是将它们赶尽杀绝 - 戈德斯坦恩 她在哪
instead of killing them. -Goldstein! Where is she?
她在哪 戈德斯坦恩
Where is she? Goldstein!
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein!
你又插手调查小组的事了
Did you just butt in on the Investigative Team again?
- 你之前到哪去了 - 什么
- Where've you been? -What?
- 她是在哪把你捞来的 - 我吗
Where'd she pick you up? -Me?
你又开始追踪他们
Have you been tracking them
- 又是第二塞勒姆人组织吗 - 当然没有 头儿
Second Salemers again? -Of course not, sir.
- 下午好 格雷夫斯先生 - 下午好 艾伯纳西
Afternoon, Mr. Graves, sir! -Afternoon, Abernathy.
艾伯纳西先生 这是斯卡曼德
Mr. Graves, sir, this is Mr. Scamander.
他的箱子里有个神奇动物
He has a crazy creature in that case
结果它跑了出来 在银行引发了骚乱
and it got out and caused mayhem in a bank, sir.
拿出来让我们看看
Let's see the little guy.
但是 先生
But, sir...
蒂娜
Tina...
对不起 奶奶
I'm sorry, Grandma.
我的妈咪 你的妈咪 要去抓女巫
My momma, your momma, gonna catch a witch.
我的妈咪 你的妈咪 挥舞小棒子
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
巫师就在我们身边
加入新塞勒
姆人大军！
我的妈咪 你的妈咪 女巫不哭泣
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
我的妈咪 你的妈咪 女巫必须死
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
女巫一号 淹死在河里
Witch number one, drown in a river!
女巫二号 赶上绞刑架
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
女巫三号 看她烧成灰
Witch number three, gonna watch her burn.
女巫四号 鞭打直转圈
Witch number four, flogging take a turn.
把传单拿好才给饭吃哦 孩子们
Collect your leaflets before you get food, children.
这是个巫师标志吗 女士
Is it a witch's mark, ma'am?
不 他不是巫师
No. He's okay.
真不敢相信你没有清除那个人的记忆
I can't believe you didn't obliviate that man!
上头要是追问起来 我就玩完
If there's an inquiry, I'm finished!
- 你为什么会玩完 我才是惹事的那一个
-So why would you be finished? I'm the one that's...
我不该去靠近第二塞勒姆人的地盘
I'm not supposed to go near the Second Salemers!
那又是什么
What was that?
呃 蛾子 我觉得 是只大飞蛾
Er... moth, I think. Big moth.
嘿 大家静一静 我有话要说
Hey, quiet down. I'm trying to get a statement.
我话撂这儿 如果又是煤气爆炸
I'm telling you it's a gas explosion again.
在彻底安全之前
I ain't taking the kids
我是绝不会带孩子们回这里的 - 抱歉 女士
back up there until it's safe. -Sorry, ma'am.
- 这可没有煤气的味道 - 这不是煤气造成的 - 长官 我之前见过
There ain't no smell of gas. -It wasn't gas, Officer, I seen it!
那是个 十分 十分 巨大的...煤气...
It wuzza... A gigantic... A huge hippopotto gas. Gas.
我不知道
I don't know.
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
箱子打开过
It was open?
- 就开了一下下...- 那个疯嗅嗅又跑出来了
Just a smidge... -That crazy Niffler thing's on the loose again?
- 应该吧 - 那去找啊 去找
- It might be. -Then look for it! Look!
他脖子在流血 他受伤了
His neck's bleeding, he's hurt!
醒醒 麻鸡先生
Wake up, Mr. No-Maj.
天哪 那是什么
Mercy Lewis, what is that?
- 没什么 就是只莫特拉鼠而已
-Nothing to worry about. That is a Murtlap.
你那箱子里还有什么东西
What else have you got in there?
- 是你 - 你好啊
- You! -Hello.
- 放松 - 科瓦尔斯基 雅各布
- Easy, Mr... -Kowalski... Jacob.
你不能对他用遗忘咒 他得当我们的目击证人
You can't obliviate him! We need him as a witness.
抱歉 你刚刚就因为
I'm sorry, you've just yelled at me the
我没有第一时间对他施遗忘咒冲我嚷嚷了一路
length of New York for not doing it in the first place.
- 他受伤了 看起来伤得很严重 - 他会好的
- He's hurt! He looks ill! -He'll be fine.
莫特拉鼠的咬伤不是很严重
Murtlap bites aren't serious.
不过我承认他是比一般情况反映强烈一些
I admit that is a slightly more severe reaction than I've seen,
但如果很严重的话 他应该
but if it was really serious, he'd have...
什么
What?
初期征兆是会从屁屁里喷出
Well, the first symptom would be flames out of
- 火焰 - 这太荒唐了
- his anus... -This is balled up!
最多持续48小时
It'll last forty-eight hours at most!
如果你想的话我可以把他留下来
I can keep him if you want me to.
留下他 我们不能留他们 斯卡曼德先生
Oh, keep him? We don't keep them! Mr. Scamander,
如果你想的话我可以把他留下来
I can keep him if you want me to.
留下他 我们不能留他们 斯卡曼德先生
Oh, keep him? We don't keep them! Mr. Scamander,
你对美国的巫师协会就没有一点点了解吗
do you know anything about the wizarding community in America?
其实我还是了解一些的
I do know a few things, actually.
我知道你们的法律
I know you have rather backwards
对我们与麻鸡的关系有着严格的规定
laws about relations with non-magic people.
像什么不能和他们做朋友啊
That you're not meant to befriend them,
不能和他们结婚啊
that you can't marry them,
- 我觉得都有点荒唐 - 谁要跟他结婚啊
- which seems mildly absurd to me. -Who's going to marry him?
你们俩都跟我走
You're both coming with me.
我不懂我为什么要跟你走
I don't see why I need to come with you.
- 来搭把手 - 我是不是在做梦
- Help me! -I'm dreaming, right?
- 帮个忙 - 啊 我累了 我没去过银行
- Please. -Yeah, I'm tired, I never went to the bank.
这不过是场噩梦对不对
This is all just some big nightmare, right?
对我们来说都是噩梦 科瓦尔斯基先生
For the both of us, Mr. Kowalski.
这里就是新闻编辑部 我们走吧
And so this is the newsroom. Let's go.
嗨 你好吗 为拜尔本一家让个路好吗
Hey, how are you? Make way for the Barebones!
用他们的说法 他们现在正在把文章放在床上
Now, they're just putting the papers to bed, as they say.
先生 肖先生现在正在和议员谈事情
Mr. Shaw, sir, he's with the senator.
那都不是事儿 巴克 我要见我父亲
Never mind that, Barker, I wanna see my father!
抱歉 肖先生 您的儿子执意要进来
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw, but your son insisted.
父亲 你听见这件事会很高兴的
Father, you're going to want to hear this.
抱歉 肖先生 您的儿子执意要进来
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw, but your son insisted.
父亲 你听见这件事会很高兴的
Father, you're going to want to hear this.
我拿到了个大新闻
I've got something huge!
我和你哥哥正忙着呢
Your brother and I are busy here,
兰登 我们正为他的选举作准备
Langdon. Working on his election campaign.
没空理你
We don't have time for this.
这位是玛丽 露 拜尔本
This is Mary Lou Barebone
来自新塞勒姆保护协会
from the New Salem Preservation Society,
- 她给你带了个大新闻 - 是吗
- and she's got a big story for you! -Oh, she has, has she?
这座城市正在发生许许多多奇怪的事
There's strange things going on all over the city.
这些事情的幕后黑手 并不是像你我这样的人
The people behind this, they are not like you and me.
这是因为魔法 看见了吗
This is witchcraft, don't you see.
- 兰登 - 她不是想要钱
-Langdon. -She doesn't want any money.
那要么她的故事不值钱
Then either her story is worthless,
要么她虚报了价格
or she's lying about the cost.
不会有人白给别人有价值的信息的
Nobody gives away anything valuable for free,
您说的没错 肖先生
You are right, Mr. Shaw.
我们想要的东西
What we desire is infinitely
比金钱有价值的多 就是您的影响力
more valuable than money: It's your influence.
数百万人阅读您的报纸
Millions of people read your newspapers
而他们需要知道危险的存在
and they need to be made aware about this danger.
地铁里出现了疯狂骚动 你看看这些照片啊
The crazy disturbances in the subway, just look at the pictures!
我想请你和你的朋友们离开
I'd like you and your friends to leave.
不 你会错过这个机会的
No, you're missing a trick here.
- 你看一眼证据啊 - 是吗 - 兰登
- Just look at the evidence. -Really. -Langdon.
听父亲的话出去吧 然后
Just listen to Father and go. And...
顺便把这些怪胎都带走
Take the freaks with you.
- 这是父亲的办公室 不是你的 - 好吧
-This is Father's office, not yours. -Okay.
而且我已经厌倦了
And I'm sick of this every
- 我每次走进来 - 好了 谢谢你们
- time I walk in here... -That's it. Thank you.
我们希望您可以重新考虑一下 肖先生
We hope you'll reconsider, Mr. Shaw.
我们并不难找
We're not difficult to find.
感谢您抽出宝贵时间听我们说话
Until then, we thank you for your time.
喂 小伙子
Hey, boy.
你掉东西了
You dropped something.
给你 怪胎 你为什么不
Here you go, freak. Why don't
把这些垃圾扔进你该待的垃圾桶里呢
you put that in the trash where you all belong.
这边右转
Take a right here.
好了 在我们进去之前
Okay, before we go in...
我是不能把男人带进屋子里的
I'm not supposed to have men on the premises.
这样的话 我和科瓦尔斯基先生
In that case, Mr. Kowalski and I can
- 可以随便找个其他的地方住 - 哦不 你们不能
- easily seek other accommodation. -Oh no, you don't!
小心脚下
Watch your step.
是你吗 蒂娜
That you, Tina?
- 是的 埃斯波西托太太 - 你自己吗
- Yes, Mrs. Esposito! -Are you alone?
我从来都是一个人啊 埃斯波西托太太
I'm always alone, Mrs. Esposito!
小蒂 你带男人回家了
Teenie, you brought men home?
先生们 这位是我妹妹
Gentlemen, this is my sister.
- 你是不是该去穿个衣服 奎妮 - 当然
= You want to put something on, Queenie? -Sure.
- 他们是谁 - 那位是斯卡曼德先生
- So, who are they? -That's Mr. Scamander.
他正致力于一件
He's committed a serious
严重违反国家保密条例的事情
infraction of the National Statute of Secrecy.
- 他是罪犯吗 - 嗯哼
- He's a criminal? -Uh-huh.
- 这位是科瓦尔斯基先生 是个麻鸡 - 麻鸡
- And this is Mr. Kowalski, he's a No-Maj. -A No-Maj?
- 小蒂 你把他们带来干什么 - 他病了 说来话长
- Teen, what are you up to? -He's sick, it's a long story.
斯卡曼德先生丢了点东西 我要帮他找回来
Mr. Scamander has lost something, I'm going to help him find it.
你得坐下来 亲爱的 他一天都没吃过东西了
You need to sit down, honey. Hey, he hasn't eaten all day.
真是糟糕 他没有拿到他开面包房需要的资金
That's rough, he didn't get the money he wanted for his bakery.
你会烤面包吗 亲爱的
You bake, honey?
- 我很喜欢烹饪 - 你会摄魂取念
- I love to cook. -You're a Legilimens?
嗯 是的 但我不太会
Uh-huh, yeah. But I always have
读你这类人的思想 英国人 主要是口音问题
trouble with your kind. Brits. It's the accent.
- 你会读心 - 别担心 亲爱的
- You know how to read minds? -Don't worry, honey.
大多数人第一次见到我的时候 想的都是和你一样的东西
Most guys think what you was thinking, first time they see me.
现在你需要吃饭
Now, you need food.
- 又吃热狗 - 别读我想法
- Hot dog... again? -Don't read my mind!
午饭吃的可不健康啊
Not a very wholesome lunch.
嗨 斯卡曼德先生
Hey, Mr. Scamander,
你想要馅饼还是果馅卷
you prefer pie or strudel?
我都好
I really don't have a preference.
你喜欢果馅卷是吗 亲爱的
You prefer strudel, huh, honey?
那就做果馅卷
Strudel it is.
好了 请坐 斯卡曼德先生
Well, sit down, Mr. Scamander.
我们不会给你下毒的
We're not going to poison you.
你很难过 又是因为你的母亲
You're upset. It's your mother again.
一定是有人说了什么 他们说什么了 告诉我
Somebody's said something, what did they say? Tell me.
- 你觉得我是怪胎吗 - 不
- Do you think I'm a freak? -No,
我觉得你是个非常特别的年轻人
I think you're a very special young man
要不然我是不会找你帮忙的 现在可以帮我忙了吗
or I wouldn't have asked you to help me, now would I?
- 你有什么新消息吗 - 我还在找
- Have you any news? -I'm still looking.
格雷夫斯先生 如果我知道他是男孩还是女孩
Mr. Graves, if I knew whether it was a girl or boy...
我的幻视只显示了那个孩子强大的力量
My vision showed only the child's immense power.
他或者她不超过十岁
He or she is no older than ten,
而且我看到这孩子离你妈妈很近
and I saw this child in close proximity to your mother.
我很清楚的看见了她
She I saw so plainly.
- 那他可能是数百个孩子中的任何一个 - 还有其他事
- That could be any one of hundreds. -There is something else.
还有件我没告诉你的事情 在纽约的时候 我看到你就在我身边
Something I haven't told you. I saw you beside me in New York.
你就是赢得这孩子信任的人
You're the one that gains this child's trust.
你就是关键 我看到了
You are the key, I saw this.
你想加入巫术的世界
You want to join the wizarding world.
我也想 克雷登斯 我想让你的愿望成真
I want those things too, Credence. I want them for you.
去找那个孩子吧 找到那个孩子我们的任务就都完成了
So find the child. Find the child and we'll all be free.
这工作没听起来那么好
The job ain't that glamorous.
我几乎每天都在泡咖啡
I mean, I spend most days making coffee,
跑跑洗手间 蒂娜才是那种职业女性
unjinxing the john. Tina's the career girl.
我们是孤儿
Nah. We're orphans. Ma
父母在我们小时候得龙痘去世了
and Pa died of dragon pox when we were kids.
你真贴心 但我们还有彼此啊
You're sweet. But we got each other!
你能先别读我的想法吗
Could you stop reading my mind for a second?
别误会 我挺喜欢那样的
Don't get me wrong, I love it.
这顿饭 太好吃了 我就是干这个的 我是个厨师
This meal, it's insanely good! This is what I do, I'm a cook.
而这顿饭 好像是我这辈子吃过最好吃的饭了
And this is, like, the greatest meal I have ever had in my life.
太逗了 我之前还从没和麻鸡说过话呢
Oh, you slay me! I ain't never really talked to a No-Maj before.
真的吗
Really?
我不是在调情
I am not flirting!
我就想说 别对他产生感情
I'm just saying, don't go getting attached,
他终归会被施遗忘咒的
he's going to have to be obliviated!
不是针对你
It's nothing personal.
- 嘿 你还好吗 亲爱的 - 戈德斯坦恩小姐
- Hey, you okay, honey? -Miss Goldstein,
我想科瓦尔斯基先生应该早点休息了
I think Mr. Kowalski could do with an early night.
对了 你和我明天早上
And besides, you and I will need to
得早起去找我的嗅嗅 所以
be up early tomorrow morning to find my Niffler, so...
- 嗅嗅是什么 - 别问
- What's a Niffler? - Don't ask.
你们可以睡在这里
Okay, you guys can bunk in here.
我觉得你们可能会想喝杯热饮
I thought you might like a hot drink?
斯卡曼德先生 看 是热可可诶
Hey, Mr. Scamander... Look, cocoa!
- 卫生间走到走廊尽头右转 - 非常
- The toilet's down the hall to the right. -Thanks...
感谢
Very much.
来
Come on.
我的天
For the love of...
- 请坐 - 好的
- Will you sit down? -Good idea.
肯定是莫特拉鼠咬的
That's definitely the Murtlap.
你肯定是极易受影响的那种人
You must be particularly susceptible.
喏 你是个麻瓜 所以我们的生理机能略有不同
See, you're a Muggle. So our physiologies are subtly different.
坐好别动 这个应该可以抑制发汗
Stay still. Now that should stop the sweating.
这里面还有一种可以抑制抽搐
And one of those should sort the twitch.
拿着
Take that.
来
Come on...
- 你拿的是什么 - 这个 本地人叫他蜷翼魔
- What you got there? -This the locals call “Swooping Evil”,
名字听起来不怎么美好 不过他很灵敏的
not the friendliest of names. It's quite an agile fellow.
我正在研究他 我相当肯定他的毒液
I've been studying him. And I am pretty sure his venom
经过稀释后对抹除不好的记忆
could be quite useful if properly diluted.
有很大的用处
Just to remove bad memories, you know.
不过可能不该在这里把他放出来
Probably shouldn't let him loose in here, though.
来吧
Come on.
来 到下面来
Come on. Down you come.
乖
Come on.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank Paracelsus.
你要是跑出去了可会出大事的
If you'd have got out that could have been quite catastrophic.
看 他就是我来美国的原因
You see, he's the real reason I came to America.
送弗兰克回家
To bring Frank home.
抱歉别过来 他有点害怕陌生人
No, sorry, stay there, he's a wee bit sensitive to strangers.
好了 好了 没事 他是被走私过去的
Here you are, here you are. He was trafficked, you see.
我在埃及找到了他 他当时被锁了起来
I found him in Egypt, he was all chained up.
我不能把它丢在那 得把他带回来
Couldn't leave him there, had to bring him back.
我要把你带回家的 对不对 弗兰克
I'm going to put you back where you belong, aren't I, Frank?
带回亚利桑那州的原野之中
To the wilds of Arizona.
- 他们来了 - 谁来了 - 角驼兽
- Here they come. -Here who comes? -The Graphorns.
没事儿 不会有事儿的
You're all right. You're all right.
你好呀 你好呀
Hello, hello!
他们是仅存的一对角驼兽了
So they're the last breeding pair in existence.
如果我没把他们救出来
If I hadn't managed to rescue them,
角驼兽就已经灭绝了
that could have been the end of Graphorns, forever.
好了
All right.
- 你救的这些动物 - 是的 没错
- What, you rescue these creatures? -Yes, that's right.
解救他们 养育他们 然后保护他们
Rescue, nurture, and protect them,
我正在努力让我的巫师同伴接受他们
and I'm gently trying to educate my fellow wizards about them.
跟我来
Come on.
提图斯 芬恩 波比 马洛 汤姆
Titus? Finn? Poppy, Marlow, Tom?
他感冒了 他需要人体的温暖
He had a cold. He needed some body warmth.
好了 上去吧
Right, on you hop.
看见了吧 他有点黏人 过去吧 皮克特
See, he has some attachment issues. Now, come on, Pickett.
他们不会欺负你的 去吧
Pickett. No, they're not going to bully you. Now, come on.
皮克特
Pickett!
那好吧 难怪它们都说我偏心
All right. But that is exactly why they accuse me of favoritism.
杜戈尔哪儿去了
I wonder where Dougal's gone.
好啦 来啦来啦 妈妈在这儿 妈妈在这儿
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming, Mum's here. Mum's here.
- 你好呀 让我好好看看你 - 我见过这些小家伙
- Hello, you, let me take a look at you. - I know these guys.
- 你的鸟蛇 - 什么意思 你是说我的鸟蛇
- Your Occamy. - What do you mean? My Occamy?
是的 你想不想
Yes, do you want to...
当然想啦
Yeah, sure. Okay.
- 嘿 - 对不起 不要摸它的头
- Hey. - No, sorry, don't pet them.
它们早就已经学会保护自己了 你看
They learn to defend themselves early. See,
他们的蛋壳都是银的 所以非常珍贵
their shells are made of silver so they're incredibly valuable.
- 好吧 - 他们的巢很容易被猎人洗劫
- Okay. - Their nests tend to get ransacked by hunters.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 斯卡曼德先生 - 叫我纽特
- Mr. Scamander? - Call me Newt.
纽特 我想我不是在作梦
Newt, I don't think I'm dreaming.
- 你是怎么发现的 - 我没有那么好的想像力
- What gave it away? - I ain't got the brains to make this up.
你能帮我把这些小肉球
Actually, would you mind throwing
扔给那边的拜月兽吗
some of those pellets in with the Mooncalves over there?
- 当然可以 - 就在那儿
- Yeah, sure. - Just over there...
糟了 嗅嗅不见了 这个小淘气
Bugger, Niffler's gone. Of course he has, little bugger.
绝不能让它看到任何亮晶晶的东西
Any chance to get his hands on something shiny.
今天怎么样啊 雅各布
What did you do today, Jacob?
我一直待在手提箱里
I was inside a suitcase.
小伙子们 你们好啊 好啦好啦
Hey. Hello, fellas. All right, all right.
慢慢来 慢慢来
Take it easy, take it easy.
小可爱 在这儿呢
Cutie. There it is.
- 退后 - 天哪
- Step back. -Jeez...
- 退后 - 这玩意儿怎么了
- Step back. - What's the matter with this?
- 我说了让开 - 好吧
- I said step away. - Yeah.
- 退后 - 这玩意儿怎么了
- Step back. - What's the matter with this?
- 我说了让开 - 好吧
- I said step away. - Yeah.
- 这是个什么东西 - 默默然
- What the hell is this thing? - It's an Obscurus.
我要在它们受到伤害之前
I need to get going,
把他们全部找回来
find everyone who's escaped before they get hurt.
- 在它们受到伤害之前 - 是的
- Before they could get hurt? - Yes,
科瓦尔斯基先生 它们现在身处陌生环境
Mr. Kowalski. They're currently in alien terrain,
身旁围绕着
surrounded by millions
数百万极残忍的生物
of the most vicious creatures on the planet.
人类
Humans.
你说 像这样一个
So where would you say that a
中等大小 喜欢开阔的平原
medium-sized creature that likes broad, open plains,
树木 水坑那样的小家伙 她会去哪儿呢
trees, water holes, that kind of thing, where might she go?
纽约有这种地方吗 - 有 - 平原之类的吗
- In New York City? - Yes. - Plains?
- 中央公园 - 具体在哪儿 - 中央公园在哪儿
Central Park? - And where is that exactly? - Where is Central Park?
好吧 我可以带你去
Well, look, I would come and show you,
但你不觉得这样对不起那两姐妹吗
but don't you think it's kind of a double cross?
她们好心招待我们 又为我们泡可可
The girls take us in, they make us hot cocoa.
你别忘了 当他们看到你病好了
You do realize that when they see you've stopped sweating,
就会对你施遗忘咒
they'll obliviate you in a heartbeat.
什么是 遗忘咒
What does “Bliviate” mean?
就是当你一觉醒来 所有关于魔法的记忆都被抹去了
It'll be like you wake up and all memory of magic is gone.
- 我就不记得这些事了吗 - 是的
- I won't remember any of this? - No.
那好吧 我帮你
All right, yeah, okay, I'll help you.
那走吧
Come on, then.
克里登斯 你去哪儿了
Credence, where have you been?
我去找明天要集会的地方了
I was looking for a place for tomorrow's meeting.
第三十二大街的转角 那里可以
There's a corner on Thirty-Second Street that could...
对不起 妈妈 我不知道都已经这么晚了
I'm sorry, Ma. I didn't realize it was so late.
- 吃饭的时候我一直在观察你 - 怎么了
- I was watching you at dinner. - Yeah.
大家喜欢你 对吗 科瓦尔斯基先生
People like you, don't they, Mr. Kowalski?
我想大家也都很喜欢你
Well, I'm sure people like you too, huh?
你错了 大家都觉得我挺讨厌
No, not really. I annoy people.
你为什么想要做面包师
Why did you decide to be a baker?
因为我觉得在罐头工厂工作没有意义
Well, because I'm dying in that canning factory.
大家都累得要死 就好像被榨干了一样
Everyone there's dying. It just crushes the life outta you.
- 你喜欢罐头吗 - 不喜欢
- You like canned food? - No.
我也不喜欢 所以我才想做糕点
Yeah. Me neither. That's why I want to make pastries,
你懂的 它让人快乐 这边走
you know. It makes people happy. We're going this way.
那你的贷款办下来了吗
So did you get your loan?
没 我没有可抵押的东西
No, I ain't got no collateral.
显然是在军队里呆久了 我连这都不知道
Stayed in the army too long, apparently, I don't know.
- 你参军打过仗 - 我当然打过仗
- You fought in the war? - Of course I fought in the war,
大家都参军打仗了啊 难道你没有
everyone fought in the war. You didn't fight in the war?
我大部份时间和火龙 乌克兰铁肚皮一起
I worked mostly with dragons, Ukrainian Ironbellies,
在东方战线
Eastern Front.
破窗
Finestra.
飞来飞去
Accio!
这下好了 高兴了吧
All right? Happy?
抓到一个 还剩俩
One down, two to go.
- 它们往那边跑了 警官 - 举起手来
- They went that way, Officer. -Hands up!
那是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
狮子
Lion...
你知道吗 纽约实在是
You know, New York is
比我想象中有意思多了
considerably more interesting than I'd expected.
- 把这个戴上 - 我戴这个干嘛
- Put this on. - Why would I have to wear something like this?
让你的头骨
Because your skull is
不会因重击而碎裂
susceptible to breakage under immense force.
我们还给他们做了热可可
But we made 'em cocoa.
是啊
Right.
- 好了 再把这个穿上 - 好啊
- Okay, if you just, pop this on. - Okay.
那就绝对万无一失啦
Now, there's absolutely nothing for you to worry about.
告诉我 谁会信
Tell me, has anyone ever
你说的 不用担心 这样的话
believed you when you told them not to worry?
我始终相信 担心总是多余的
My philosophy is that worrying means you suffer twice.
她现在出于发情期 她需要个配偶
She's in season. She needs to mate.
毒角兽的麝香会让她疯狂
Erumpent musk, she is mad for it.
乖乖
Good girl...
来吧 到箱子里来
Come on, into the case.
不要啊
Oh, no.
雷帕尔
Repar...
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard!
梅林的胡
法世界感叹语
相当于oh my god
他俩完全一样
They're exactly the same.
- 一样的 - 纽特
- Same thing. -Newt!
啊 啊 啊 不要啊
No, no, no, don't!
对不起
I'm so sorry.
做得好 科瓦尔斯基先生
Good show, Mr. Kowalski!
叫我雅各布
Call me Jacob.
抓到二个 还剩一个
Two down, one to go.
快跳下去吧
In you hop.
女士们 先生们 今晚的演讲者
Ladies and gentlemen, tonight's keynote speaker
应该不需要我再多做介绍
needs no introduction from me.
已经有人叫他未来的总统
He's been mentioned as a future president.
如果你不相信 就看看他爸爸的报纸
And if you don't believe me, just read his daddy's newspapers.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen, I
让我们欢迎纽约参议员 亨利 肖
give you the senator for New York, Henry Shaw!
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you!
谢谢大家
Thank you.
我们的确取得了一些进展
And it's true we have made some progress,
但懒惰是没有回报的
but there is no reward for idleness.
所以 饮酒玩乐的酒吧已被封禁
So just as the odious saloons have been banished...
发生什么事了
What's going on?
而现在这些台球厅和私人包厢
So now the pool halls, and these private parlors...
那是什么
What is that?
女巫
Witches!
我们的美国朋友
Our American friends have
已经同意了保密协议
permitted a breach of the Statute of Secrecy,
还恐吓说要把我们暴露出去
that threatens to expose us all.
我不会被那个
I will not be lectured by the man
让盖勒特 格林德沃从他手里溜走的人教训
who let Gellert Grindelwald slip through his fingers.
主席阁下 抱歉打断您的话 但情况紧急
Madam President, I'm so sorry to interrupt, but this is critical.
你就这么闯进来
You'd better have an excellent
最好有充分的理由 戈德斯坦小姐
excuse for this intrusion, Miss Goldstein.
是的 我有
Yes, I do.
阁下 昨天有个巫师提着一个箱子来到纽约
Ma'am. Yesterday a wizard entered New York with a case.
这个箱子里装满了神奇动物
This case full of magical creatures,
不幸的是 有的动物跑出来了
and unfortunately, some have escaped.
他是昨天来的
He arrived yesterday?
你24小时前就知道 有个未经登记的巫师
You have known for twenty-four hours that an unregistered wizard
让神奇动物在纽约大肆逃跑
set magical beasts loose in New York
而你却等到有人被杀了才来告诉我们这件事
and you see fit to tell us only when a man has been killed?
- 谁被杀了 - 这人现在哪里
- Who has been killed? - Where is this man?
斯卡曼德
Scamander?
- 你好 部长 - 提修斯 斯卡曼德 战争英雄
- Hello, Minister. - Theseus Scamander? The war hero?
不 这是他的弟弟
No, this is his little brother.
你来纽约做什么
And what are you doing in New York?
我来买阿帕卢萨小毛球 长官
I came to buy an Appaloosa Puffskein, sir. -Right.
你来这里的真实目的是什么
What are you really doing here?
戈德斯坦 他又是谁
Goldstein, and who is this?
这位是雅各布 科瓦尔斯基先生 总统女士
This is Jacob Kowalski, Madam President,
他是被斯卡曼德先生的神奇动物咬伤的麻鸡
he's a No-Maj who got bitten by one of Mr. Scamander's creatures.
- 麻鸡 - 遗忘咒呢
- No-Maj? - Obliviated?
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard.
你知道这是哪个神奇动物干的吗 斯卡曼德先生
You know which of your creatures was responsible, Mr. Scamander?
- 这不是神奇动物干的 - 别装了
No creature did this. Don't pretend!
你们难道看不出来吗 看看他的伤口
You must know what that was, look at the marks...
是默默然
That was an Obscurus.
你太过分了 斯卡曼德先生
You go too far, Mr. Scamander.
美国根本就没有默然者
There is no Obscurial in America.
没收这个箱子 格雷夫斯
Impound that case, Graves!
- 等下 不可以 还给我 - 把它们都抓起来
- Wait. No. Give that back. - Arrest them!
不要伤害那些动物
Don't hurt those creatures.
求你了 你不明白
Please, you don't understand,
里面的东西没有危险 没有
nothing in there is dangerous, nothing!
我们自会评判 把它们关起来
We'll be the judges of that! Take them to the cells!
不要伤害那些动物 它们并不危险
Don't hurt those creatures, nothing in there is dangerous!
求你了 不要伤害我的动物
Please, don't hurt my creatures!
它们不危险 求你了
They aren't dangerous! Please, they are not dangerous!
它们不危险
They are not dangerous!
对于你的神奇动物我很抱歉 斯卡曼德先生
I am so sorry about your creatures, Mr. Scamander.
真的很抱歉
I truly am.
谁能告诉我
Can someone please tell me
什么是默默然吗
what this Obscurial-Obscurius thing is? Please?
几个世纪没出现过了
There hasn't been one for centuries.
3个月前我在苏丹见过一个
I met one in Sudan three months ago.
以前有很多 现在也还是有的
There used to be more of them but they still exist.
在巫师被迫躲起来之前
Before wizards went underground,
就在我们还在被麻瓜追杀的时候
when we were still being hunted by Muggles,
年轻的巫师和女巫试图隐藏自己的魔法
young wizards and witches sometimes tried to suppress their magic
以免遭到迫害
to avoid persecution.
但他们没有去学怎样控制自己的力量
Instead of learning to harness or to control their powers,
而是钻研出了默默然这样的东西
they developed what was called an Obscurus.
它极不稳定
It's an unstable,
不受控制的黑暗力量会突然爆发和攻击
uncontrollable Dark force that busts out and attacks...
然后销声匿迹
And then vanishes.
默然者都活不长久 是不是
Obscurials can't survive long, can they?
据现存的史料记载
There's no documented case
默然者还没有活过十年的
of any Obscurial surviving past the age of ten.
我在非洲见到的那只活了8年
The one I met in Africa was eight when she...
她死的时候才8岁
She was eight when she died.
现在你是跟我说
What are you telling me here,
参议员肖是被一个孩子杀死的
that Senator Shaw was killed by a kid?
我的妈咪，你的妈咪，挥舞小棒子
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
我的妈咪，你的妈咪，女巫不哭泣
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
我的妈咪，你的妈咪，女巫必须死
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
女巫一号 淹死在河里
Witch number one, drown in a river!
女巫二号 推上绞刑架
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
- 把传单发出去 - 女巫三号
- Hand out your leaflets! - Witch number three...
要是你把传单丢了 我会知道的
I'll know if you dump 'em.
看到什么可疑的东西 要回来告诉我
Tell me if you see anything suspicious.
很高兴认识你 雅各布
It was good to make your acquaintance, Jacob
希望你能开个属于自己的面包坊
and I hope you get your bakery.
- 斯卡曼德先生 你还真是个有趣的人 - 格雷夫斯先生
- You're an interesting man, Mr. Scamander. - Mr. Graves...
你因害危及他人性命而被霍格沃兹开除
You were thrown out of Hogwarts for endangering human life...
- 那只是个意外 - 与野兽为伍
- That was an accident! - With a beast.
但还是有一个教你的老师强烈反对开除你
Yet one of your teachers argued strongly against your expulsion.
是什么让阿不思 邓不利多如此钟爱你呢
What makes Albus Dumbledore so fond of you?
我真的不能说
I really couldn't say.
所以放装一箱子的危险动物到这也是
So setting a pack of dangerous creatures loose here was...
只是个意外 对吗
Was just another accident, is that right?
我为什么要故意这样做
Why would I do it deliberately?
为了揭发巫师世界
To expose wizardkind.
为了挑起魔法世界和麻鸡世界的纷争
To provoke war between the magical and non-magical worlds.
你是说为了追求更大的利益而进行大规模的屠杀
Mass slaughter for the greater good, you mean?
对 就是这样
Yes. Quite.
格雷夫斯先生 我可不是格林德沃的狂热分子
I'm not one of Grindelwald's fanatics, Mr. Graves.
斯卡曼德先生 我在想对这个你还有什么话可说
I wonder what you can tell me about this, Mr. Scamander?
这是默默然 但不是你想的那样
It's an Obscurus. But it's not what you think.
在我试图救一个苏丹女孩时
I managed to separate it
成功将它从她体里分离了出来
from the Sudanese girl as I tried to save her.
想把它带回家 研究研究
Wanted to take it home, to study it.
它出了那只箱子就存活不了了
But it cannot survive outside that box,
它伤不了人的 蒂娜
it could not hurt anyone, Tina!
所以没有宿主它就没用了
So it's useless without the host?
没用 你说没用
"Useless?" "Useless?"
那神奇力量可是能够寄身进而杀死一个小孩的啊
That is a parasitical magical force that killed a child.
你是要用它干嘛吗
What on earth would you use it for?
斯卡曼德先生 你骗不了任何人
You fool nobody, Mr. Scamander.
你将这只默默然带进
You brought this Obscurus into the
纽约城就是想造成大规模的破坏
city of New York in the hope of causing mass disruption,
打破保密法令 然后揭露魔法世界
breaking the Statute of Secrecy and revealing the magical world.
你知道这个默默然谁也害不了的 你知道的
You know that can't hurt anyone, you know that!
你因背叛同门魔法师罪
You are therefore guilty of a treasonous betrayal
而被处以死刑
of your fellow wizards and are sentenced to death.
戈德斯坦恩小姐因是你的帮凶
Miss Goldstein, who has aided and abetted you...
不 她跟这事没关系
No, she's done nothing of the kind.
她将与你同刑
She receives the same sentence.
立刻行刑
Just do it immediately.
- 我将亲自去通知皮克科瑞主席 - 蒂娜
- I will inform President Picquery myself. - Tina.
请吧
Please.
伯纳黛特 不要这样 求求你
Don't do this, Bernadette, please...
不会痛的
It don't hurt.
- 蒂娜 - 妈妈 - 蒂娜
- Tina... -Momma... - Tina...
过来吧 小可爱 该睡觉觉了 准备好了吗
Come on, pumpkin, time for bed. Are you ready?
多好呀你看
Don't that look good?
你想进去吗
You wanna get in? Huh?
- 嗨 山姆 - 嗨 奎妮 - 楼下叫你呢
- Hey, Sam! - Hey, Queenie. - They need you downstairs.
- 我来给这家伙施遗忘咒 - 你没这个资格
I'll obliviate this guy. -You ain't qualified.
嘿 山姆 塞西莉知道你一直在与鲁比见面吗
Hey, Sam, does Cecily know you been seeing Ruby?
- 你怎么 - 让我来给这家伙
- How'd you... - Let me obliviate
施遗忘咒 这样我就能保证守口如瓶
this guy and she'll never hear about it from me.
- 你这是在干嘛 - 嘘
- What are you doin'? - Shh!
小蒂有麻烦了 我听到了
Teen's in trouble, I'm trying to listen...
- 雅各布 纽特的箱子在哪 - 我想是那个叫格雷夫斯的家伙拿了
- Jacob, where's Newt's case? - I think that guy Graves took it.
- 好吧 跟我走 - 什么 你要给我施遗忘咒吗
- Okay, come on. - What? You're not gonna obliviate me?
当然不啊 你现在是我们中一员啦
Of course not, you're one of us now!
没事了
It's okay.
阿拉霍洞开
Alohomora.
开
Aberto...
他肯定是用一个特别的咒语将办公室锁住了
He would know a fancy spell to lock his office.
好了 让我来把你的好东西也亮出来吧
Okay, let's get the good stuff out of you.
巫婆
Witch!
- 它就要吞了我了 - 别慌
- It's just gonna eat me! - Don't panic!
那你告诉我该怎么做
What do you suggest I do instead?
跳
Jump.
- 你疯了吗 - 跳上去
- Are you crazy? - Jump on him.
蒂娜 听我的 我会抓住你的
Tina, listen to me. I'll catch you.
蒂娜
Tina!
我会抓住你的
I'll catch you.
蒂娜 我会抓住的 快
I've got you, Tina. Go!
快走
Come on!
- 过去 - 快走
- Coming through! - Move!
别盯着他脑袋了 快过来 过来
Leave his brains, come on! Come on!
- 那是什么 - 蜷翼魔 - 哇 我好喜欢
What is that thing? - Swooping Evil. -Well, I love it!
快进去
Get in.
奎妮
Queenie!
你去哪呀
Where you going?
我生病了 阿伯内西先生
I'm sick, Mr. Abernathy.
又生病了呀
Again?
- 哦好吧 你手上拿的啥呀 - 女生用的东西
- Well, what've you got there? - Ladies' things.
你想看看吗 我不介意的
You wanna take a look? I don't mind.
哇喔 不不用 我
Good gravy, no! I...
- 你可以走了 - 感谢
You get well now! -Thanks.
格雷登斯 你找到那个小孩了吗
Credence. Have you found the child?
- 找不到 - 把手给我
- I can't. - Show me.
嘘 孩子 我们越早找到这个小孩
Shh. My boy, the sooner we find this child,
你就能越早脱离苦海
the sooner you can put that pain in the past where it belongs.
格雷登斯 我希望你拿着这个
I want you to have this, Credence.
我一般很少给人这个
I would trust very few with it.
很少
Very few.
但你
But you...
你不一样
You're different.
你已找到那个小孩
When you find the child, touch
碰一下这个符号 我就会知道 我就会来找你
this symbol and I will know, and I will come to you.
做到这个 你将受到所有巫师的尊重 永远的
Do this and you will be honored among wizards. Forever.
格雷登斯 那个孩子就要死了
The child is dying, Credence.
时间不多了
Time is running out.
你爷爷还养过鸽子呀 我养过猫头鹰
Your grandfather kept pigeons? Mine bred owls.
- 我以前特别喜欢喂他们吃东西 - 格雷夫斯总是坚持认为
I used to love feeding 'em. - Graves always insisted
那些个骚动都是神奇动物造成的
the disturbances were caused by a beast.
我们必须把你所有的动物都抓回来
We need to catch all your creatures
这样他就不能老拿他们背黑锅了
so he can't keep using them as a scapegoat.
只有一只没找到了 杜戈尔 我的隐形兽
There's only one still missing. Dougal, my Demiguise.
- 杜戈尔 - 还有点小问题
- Dougal? - Slight problem is that...
他是隐形的
He's invisible.
- 隐形的 - 是的 大多时候 他确实
- Invisible? - Yes, most of the time... He does...
- 那你要怎么抓啊 - 无异于海底捞针
- How do you catch something that? - With immense difficulty.
- 纳尔拉克 - 什么
- Gnarlak! - Excuse me?
纳尔拉克 我还是傲罗的时候 他是我的线人
Gnarlak, he was an informant of mine when I was an Auror!
他以前常兼职做神奇动物的交易
He used to trade in magical creatures on the side.
他不会突然对追踪动物感兴趣吧
He wouldn't happen to have an interest in paw prints, would he?
他对一切能卖的东西都有兴趣
He's interested in anything he can sell.
我要怎么才能在这喝一杯呢
How do I get a drink in this joint?
怎么 没见过管家小精灵吗
What? Ain't you ever seen a house-elf before?
不不 我当然见过 我爱死管家小精灵了
No, no, of course I have. I love house-elves.
我叔叔家就是管家小精灵
My uncle's a house-elf.
是哦
Yeah...
请给我六杯咯咯水 一杯叶霸
Six shots of gigglewater and a lobe blaster, please.
所有麻鸡都像你这样吗
Are all No-Majs like you?
不  我就是我 是颜色不一样的烟火
No, I'm the only one like me.
这里大半人都被我抓过
I've arrested half of the people in here.
我可能多管闲事了但我看到了一些东西
You can tell me to mind my own business, but I saw something
在那个死亡药池那
in that death potion back there.
我看见你抱着那第二萨勒姆人的男孩
I saw you hugging that Second Salem boy.
他叫格雷登斯 他妈妈老打他
His name's Credence. His mother beats him.
她老打那些她收养的孩子
She beats all those kids she adopted,
但不知为何她最讨厌他
but she seems to hate him the most.
她就是你攻击的那个麻鸡吗
And she was the No-Maj you attacked?
我就是这么丢了工作的
That's how I lost my job.
我是为了她的狂热追随者集会而去找她的
I went for her in front of a meeting of her crazy followers.
结果他们都得施遗忘咒 是个大丑闻
They all had to be obliviated. It was a big scandal.
他来了
It's him.
这么说
So...
你就是那个带着满满一箱子怪物的家伙咯
You're the guy with the case full of monsters, huh?
坏事传千里哈
News travels fast.
我来是希望你能
I was hoping you'd be able
告诉我是否有什么眼线
to tell me if there have been any sightings.
追踪器那之类的东西
Tracks. That sort of thing.
斯卡曼德先生 你的脑袋可值不少钱啊
You've got a big price on your head, Mr. Scamander.
为什么我要帮你而不是举报你呢
Why should I help you instead of turnin' you in?
我想我得想办法说服你啦
I take it I'll have to make it worth your while?
从服务费开始谈吧
Let's consider it a cover charge.
美魔会出手可比你大多了
MACUSA's offerin' more'n that.
望月镜
Lunascope?
我有五个了
I got five.
- 冰火蛇蛋 - 你也看见了 现在我们
- Frozen Ashwinder egg! - You see, now we're...
等一下
Wait a minute.
那是护 那是护树罗锅 对吗
That's Bow... That's a Bowtruckle, right?
- 不是 - 拜托 他们会开锁 是吗
- No. - Come on. They pick locks, am I right?
- 不会给你的 - 那么
- You're not having him. - Well,
希望你们能活着回来
good luck gettin' back alive,
斯卡曼德先生 整个美魔会都在找你
Mr. Scamander, what with the whole of MACUSA on your back.
好吧
All right.
皮克特
Pickett...
某个隐形的东西一直在第五大道那肆虐
Somethin' invisible's been wreakin' havoc around Fifth Avenue.
你可以去梅西百货公司找找
You may wanna check out Macy's department store.
也许能帮你找到你要找的
Might help with what you're looking for.
杜戈尔 还有一件事
Dougal... One last thing.
美魔会里有个叫格雷夫斯的
There's a Mr. Graves who works at MACUSA.
你知道他的背景吗
I was wondering what you knew of his background.
斯卡曼德先生 你问的太多啦
You ask a lot of questions, Mr. Scamander.
那会给你招来杀身之祸
That can get you killed.
- 美魔会的人来啦 - 你给他们通风报信了
- MACUSA are coming! - You tipped them off!
对不起了 纳尔拉克先生
Sorry, Mr. Gnarlak...
让我想起了我的领班
Reminds me of my foreman!
克雷登斯 你在干嘛
What are you doin', Credence?
- 这你哪拿的 - 还给我 克雷登斯 这只是个玩具
- Where'd you get this? - Give it back, Credence. It's just a toy!
这是什么
What is this?
皮带脱下来
Take it off!
- 妈 - 我不是你妈
- Ma... - I am not your Ma!
你妈是个邪恶的 天理不容的女人
Your mother was a wicked, unnatural woman!
- 那是我妈妈 - 真是诚实啊
- It was mine. - Modesty...
什么情况
What is this?
隐形兽一般来讲是很温顺的
So Demiguises are fundamentally peaceful,
但如果被激怒的话也是会咬人的
but they can give a nasty nip if provoked.
你们两个去那边
You two, head that way.
要特别小心别被发现了
And try very hard not to be predictable.
隐形兽就是那样的吗
Was that the Demiguise?
不 我想这可能是它在这的原因
No, I think it might be the reason that the Demiguise is here.
隐形效果根据可能发生的事而变化
Its sight operates on probability,
所以它可以预见最近的未来
so it can foresee the most likely immediate future.
- 那它在干嘛 - 它在当保姆
- So what's it doing? - It's babysitting.
- 你说什么 - 这是我的错
- What did you just say? - This is my fault.
我原本以为就剩它了 但我肯定是漏数了一个
I thought I had them all, but I must have miscounted.
它就是在照顾这个吗
It was babysitting that?
鸟蛇可大可小
Occamies are choranaptyxic.
生存环境有多大它们就可以长多大
So they grow to fill available space.
妈咪在这
Mummy's here.
需要一只昆虫 随便什么昆虫还要个茶壶
We need an insect, any kind of insect and a teapot!
找个茶壶
Find a teapot!
我找到了 找到了
I got it. I got it!
茶壶
Teapot!
蟑螂丢到茶壶里
Roach in teapot...
可大可小的能力
Choranaptyxic.
他们也可以随环境缩小
They also shrink to fit the available space.
说实话
Tell me the truth.
所有从箱子里跑出来的动物
Was that everything that
都抓起来了吗 - 都抓起来了
- came out of the case? - That's everything.
真的
And that's the truth.
- 她来了 - 回家开心吗
- Here she comes. - Happy to be home?
想你肯定累坏了 小伙子 去吧 这就对了
Bet you're exhausted, buddy. Come on. There you go, that's right.
好了 我想我们得谈谈
Right. I think we need to talk.
我不会把你给他的  皮克特
I wouldn't have let him keep you, Pickett.
皮克 我宁愿死也不愿意和你分开
Pick, I would rather chop off my hand than get rid of you.
毕竟你为我做了这么多 好了啦
After everything you have done for me, now come on.
皮克 我们之前谈过生闷气的事 对吧
Pick, we've talked about sulking before, haven't we?
皮克特
Pickett...
好啦 笑一个 皮克特 给我
Come on, give me a smile. Pickett, give me a...
好吧 这可不像你哦
All right. Now, that is beneath you.
嘿 纽特
Hey Newt.
她是谁啊 谁也不是
Who is she? -That's no one.
莉塔 莱斯特兰奇 我听过这个家族
Leta Lestrange? I've heard of that family.
他们是不是有点  你知道的  不要窥探我的想法好吗
Aren't they kinda, you know? -Please don't read my mind.
- 抱歉 请你不要窥探我的想法 我懂的  - 对不起
Sorry, I asked you not to. -I know, I'm sorry.
我只是忍不住
I can't help it.
当人们内心受伤的时候
People are easiest to
- 我很容易就能读到他们的想法 - 我没有受伤
read when they're hurting. -I'm not hurting.
再说 也是很久之前的事了
Anyway, it was a long time ago.
你们在学校时 关系很亲密
That was a real close friendship you had at school.
我们两个在学校混的都不是很好
Neither of us really fitted in at school.
- 所以我们慢慢就 - 你们就亲密起来了
So we became quite... -You became real close.
这亲密关系持续了很多年
For years.
她是一个索取者  而你需要一个给予者
She was a taker. You need a giver.
你们在聊什么呢 没什么
What are you two talking about? -Nothing.
谈学校的事呢 对 学校
School. -School.
你刚才说的是学校么  有学校
Did you say school? Is there a school?
有魔法学校么  在我们美国
A wizardry school here? In America?
当然有啊 伊法摩尼魔法学校
Of course, Ilvermorny!
它是世界上最好的魔法学校
It's only the best wizard school in the whole world!
我还以为
I think you'll find the
世界上最好的魔法学校是霍格沃兹
best wizarding school in the world is Hogwarts!
才不是呢
Hogwash!
危险
Danger.
它嗅到了危险
He senses danger.
默然者刚刚在这么
The Obscurial was here?
默然者 被寄生了
黑暗魔法力量即
默默然的巫师
她去哪了
Where did she go?
救救我 救救我吧
Help me. Help me.
你不是告诉我你还有一个妹妹么
Didn't you tell me you had another sister?
求你救救我吧
Please help me.
你另一个妹妹在哪呢
Where's your other sister,
克雷登斯 - 求你了 救救我吧 小的那个妹妹呢
Credence? - Please, help me. -The little one?
她去哪了  - 求你
Where did she go? - Please...
你的妹妹现在非常危险
Your sister's in grave danger.
我们得找到她
We need to find her.
这是什么地方 这是妈妈领养摩黛丝提的地方
What is this place? -Ma adopted Modesty out of here.
妈妈从一个有12个小孩的家庭里领养的她
From a family of twelve.
她很想念她的兄弟姐妹们 她现在仍然经常谈到他们
She misses her brothers and sisters. She still talks about them.
她在哪
Where is she?
我不知道 你就是个哑炮 克雷登斯
I don't know. -You're a Squib, Credence.
我刚见到你的的时候就从你身上看出来了
I could smell it off you the minute I met you.
- 你说什么  - 你有魔法血统 但是不会用魔法
- What? - You have magical ancestry, but no power.
- 你说过你会教我的啊  - 朽木不可雕也
- But you said you could teach me. -You're unteachable.
你的妈妈死了 这就是给你的回报
Your mother's dead. That's your reward.
我们之间两清了
I'm done with you.
摩黛丝提
Modesty?
Modesty.
你不用害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
你的哥哥克雷登斯和我在一块儿
I'm here with your brother, Credence.
出来吧 现在就出来吧
Out you come, now.
克雷登斯 我欠你一句对不起
Credence, I owe you an apology.
我那么相信你
I trusted you.
我以为你是我的朋友 我以为你和其他人不一样
I thought you were my friend. That you were different.
你可以控制住自己的  克雷登斯
You can control it, Credence.
但我并不想控制 格雷夫斯先生
But I don't think I want to, Mr. Graves.
我天 这就是传说中的默然者吗
Jeez. Is that the Obscuria thing?
这东西的魔力比我听说过的任何默然者都要强大
That's more powerful than any Obscurial I have ever heard of.
如果我回不来 照顾好我的动物们
If I don't come back, look after my creatures.
你需要知道的一切都在这 - 什么
Everything that you need to know is in there. - What?
我不能让他们杀了它
They're not killing it.
纽特 你听到他说的了  照顾好他们
Newt! You heard him, look after them!
- 拿好 亲   - 不行 不行 不行
- Keep holda that, honey. - No, no, no!
我不能带你一块儿去  松手 雅各布
I can't take you. Please let go of me, Jacob!
是你说的我也是你们中的一员
You're the one that said I was one of yours,
对吧 太危险了
right? -It's too dangerous.
克雷登斯 有这个在你体内 你还能活这么久
To survive so long, with this inside you, Credence,
简直就是一个奇迹 你就是奇迹
is a miracle. You are a miracle.
加入我吧 想像一下 我们一起可以成多少事啊
Come with me, think of what we could achieve together.
纽特 是那个第二塞勒姆的男孩 他是默然者
Newt! -It's the Second Salem boy. He's the Obscurial.
但他不是小孩子啊
He's not a child.
他的魔法太强了 所以他就活下来了
His power must be so strong, he's somehow managed to survive.
纽特 救救他
Newt! Save him.
格雷夫斯
Mr. Graves.
蒂娜 你还真是阴魂不散啊
Tina. You're always turning up where you are least wanted.
用结界把这些隐藏起来 否者我们就暴露了 暴露了就会引发战争
Contain this, or we are exposed and it will mean war.
克雷登斯  克雷登斯 我可以帮助你
Credence! Credence, I can help you.
- 封锁区域 - 好的 长官 - 我不想要其他人在这儿
- Bar the area. - Yes, sir. - I don't want anyone else down there!
克雷登斯
Credence...
你是叫克雷登斯 对么
It's Credence, isn't it?
我是来帮助你的 克雷登斯
I'm here to help you, Credence.
我不是来伤害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
我之前遇到过一个和你一样的人 克雷登斯
I've met someone just like you, Credence.
一个女孩
A girl.
她被囚禁了
A young girl who'd been imprisoned,
她被关了起来 因为会魔法而遭到惩罚
she had been locked away and she'd been punished for her magic.
克雷登斯
Credence...
我能离你近一点么
Can I come over to you?
我可以过去么
Can I come over?
这个东西杀了我的儿子 我要来讨一个公道
That thing killed my son. I want justice!
我要揭露你们的真面目和你们的所作所为
I'll expose you for who you are and what you've done.
快看 拍照 快拍照
Look! Take... Take photos.
克雷登斯
Credence.
克雷登斯 不要
Credence, no!
不要这样做 求你了
Don't do this. Please.
接着说 蒂娜
Keep talking, Tina.
接着说 他会听你的 他在听你说
Keep talking to him, he'll listen to you. He's listening.
我知道那个女人对你做了些什么
I know what that woman did to you.
我知道你受了很多苦
I know that you've suffered.
但是现在你得收手了
You need to stop this now.
纽特和我会保护你的
Newt and I will protect you.
- 这个人 他只是利用你 - 不要听她瞎说 克雷登斯
This man... He is using you. -Don't listen to her, Credence.
我想给你自由
I want you to be free.
- 没事了 - 没事了
It's all right. -That's it.
站住 你们会吓到他的 放下魔杖
Don't, you'll frighten him. -Wands down!
谁要是伤了他 我唯谁是问
Anyone harms him, they'll answer to me. Credence! -Credence...
不要 不要
No. No!
- 克雷登斯  - 你们这些蠢货
Credence... You fools.
你们意识到自己刚刚犯下了什么罪过吗
Do you realize what you've done?
- 默然者是我下令杀死的 格雷夫斯 - 没错
The Obscurial was killed on my orders, Mr. Graves. -Yes.
主席阁下 历史也会记得这一点的
And history will surely note that, Madam President.
你们的决断简直是滔天大错
What was done here tonight was not right!
他得为麻鸡的死负责
He was responsible for the death of a No-Maj.
他暴露了我们魔法世界
He risked the exposure of our community.
他违背了我们最神圣的法律
He has broken one of our most sacred laws.
一部让我们就像在臭水沟里奔命的老鼠一样的法律
A law that has us scuttling like rats in the gutter!
一部让我们隐藏我们真正天性的法律
A law that demands that we conceal our true nature!
一部让它统治下的人们因为恐惧而卑躬屈膝而颤抖的法律
A law that directs those under its dominion to cower in fear
至少我们敢于开创
lest we risk discovery!
我问问你 主席阁下
I ask you, Madam President.
我问问你们所有人
I ask all of you...
这部法律究竟保护的是谁
Who does this law protect?
是我们
Us?
还是他们
Or them?
我再也不会卑躬屈膝了
I refuse to bow down any longer.
傲罗们 你们去收回格雷夫斯的魔杖
Aurors, I'd like you to relieve Mr. Graves of his wand
再把他押送回
and escort him back to...
飞来咒
Accio.
现形咒
Revelio.
你觉得你能一直关住我么
Do you think you can hold me?
我们会全力一试的 格林德沃先生
We'll do our best, Mr. Grindelwald.
会后有期 我还会回来的
Will we die, just a little?
我想得有人来看着这个东西
I figured somebody oughta keep an eye on this thing.
谢谢你 我们欠你一个对不起 斯卡曼德先生
Thank you. -We owe you an apology, Mr. Scamander.
但是魔法世界已经暴露了
But the magical community is exposed!
我们没法让全市的人都忘记
We cannot obliviate an entire city.
事实上 我想我们可以的
Actually, I think we can.
我本来打算到了亚利桑那州再跟你说再见的
I was intending to wait until we got to Arizona,
但是目前看起来你是我们唯一的希望了 弗兰克
but it seems like now you are our only hope, Frank.
我也会想你的
I'll miss you too.
你知道应该做什么
You know what you've got to do.
他们什么都不会记得
They won't remember anything.
这个药水在复原东西方面作用强大
That venom has incredibly powerful obliviative properties.
我们欠你一个大大的人情 斯卡曼德先生
We owe you a great debt, Mr. Scamander.
现在 把这个箱子带出纽约
Now, get that case out of New York.
好的 主席阁下
Yes, Madam President.
那个麻鸡还在这么
Is that No-Maj still here?
清除他的记忆 绝对不能有例外
Obliviate him. There can be no exceptions.
我很遗憾 但是一个目击者都不行  你知道法律是怎么规定的
I'm sorry, but even one witness. You know the law.
你可以好好的道个别
I'll let you say good-bye.
这样做对大家都好
This is for the best.
没错 我从头至尾就不应该在这
Yeah, I was, I was never even supposed to be here.
这些事情我都不应该知道
I was never supposed to know any of this.
大家都知道纽特让我在他身边只是因为
Everybody knows Newt only kept me around because...
纽特 你为什么让我在你身边呢
Newt, why did you keep me around?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
因为你是我的朋友
Because you're my friend
我绝对不会忘记你是怎么帮助我的 雅各布
and I'll never forget how you helped me, Jacob.
我和你一块去
I'll come with you.
我们可以去某个地方 我们可以去任何地方
We'll go somewhere, we'll go anywhere.
我再也找你到像你这样的人了
See, I ain't never gonna find anyone like.
像我的人有很多的 不是 才不是
There's loads like me. -No. No.
只有你自己才像你
There's only one like you.
我得走了
I gotta go.
雅各布 没事的 没事的
Jacob! -It's okay. It's okay.
我没事
It's okay.
就像是一觉醒来一样 对吧
It's just like waking up, right?
莫尔顿谷
对不起 对不起
So sorry, sorry!
科瓦尔斯基先生 你在罐头厂里里真是屈才了
Dear Mr. Kowalski, You are wasted in a canning factory.
请把这些鸟蛇蛋壳当作你开面包店的抵押品吧
Please take these Occamy eggshells as collateral for your bakery.
一位好心人至上
A well-wisher.
好久 是吧
It's been... -Hasn't it?
纽特 我想谢谢你
Listen, Newt, I wanted to thank you.
为什么呢
What on earth for?
你知道的  如果你没有
Well, you know, if you hadn't said
给皮克科瑞女士说了那么多我的好话
all those nice things to Madam Picquery about me,
我现在是回不到调查小组的
I wouldn't be back on the investigative team now.
这样做是因为比起其他人
Well, I can't think of
我更愿意你来调查我
anyone that I'd rather have investigating me.
尽量不要老被调查 我会的
Try not to need investigating for a bit. -I will.
从现开始我要过平静地生活了
Quiet life for me from now on.
回到魔法部之后
Back to the Ministry.
把我的手稿寄给我  我会去找的
Deliver my manuscript. -I'll look out for it.
名字是 神奇动物在哪里
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
莉塔莱斯特兰奇喜欢看书么
Does Leta Lestrange like to read?
你说谁 你带着的那张照片上的女孩儿
Who? -The girl whose picture you carry.
我不知道
I don't really know what
现在她喜欢什么 因为人是会变的
Leta likes these days because people change.
- 没错  我也变了
- Yes. -I've changed.
我觉得 或许变了一点吧
I think. Maybe a little.
- 我想送你一本我的书 如果可以的话 我很高兴
- I'll send you a copy of my book, if I may. -I'd like that.
不好意思 如果我
I'm so sorry. How would
我本人来把书送给你 你觉得怎么样
you feel if I gave you your copy in person?
我会高兴
I'd like that.
非常高兴
Very much.
科瓦尔斯基 你是怎么想到这些的 - 我不知道
Where do you get your ideas from, Mr. Kowalski? - I don't know.
我不知道怎么想到的 灵光乍现吧
I don't know. They just come.
给你 不要忘了这个 好好享受吧
Here you go. Don't forget this. Enjoy.
亨利 仓库钥匙 对吧
Hey, Henry, storage, all right?
谢啦 伙计
Thanks, pal.
Orange字幕组
倾情制作
更多作品请关注
www.orangesub.com